When Two Become One
The Twisters is a action, adventure, drama film directed by Michael Su.
A deadly patchwork of destructive cyclones is on an apocalyptic path
of convergence at a populated Midwest city center.
There, the twisters will merge into one mega tornado that threatens to
obliterate the cities for hundreds of miles around.
Dr. Janet Evans, played by Tiffany.
Dr. James Garland, played by Mark Justice.
Dr. Erica Garland, played by Kayla Fields.
Doug Cameron, played by Paul Logan.
General Murphy, played by Curtis Strong.
Claudia Santiago, played by Sofia Riba.
Twisters is a 2024 American disaster film serving as a
standalone sequel to Twister (1996).
The film was directed by Lee Isaac Chung from a screenplay by Mark L.
Smith, based on a story by Joseph Kosinski.
The ensemble cast includes Daisy Edgar-Jones, Glen Powell, Anthony
Ramos, Brandon Perea, Maura Tierney, and Sasha Lane.
It follows clashing groups of storm chasers who
investigate a tornado outbreak in Oklahoma.
Talks for a sequel to Twister began in 2020, with Kosinski pitching an idea to Universal Pictures and Helen Hunt,
who starred in the original, also expressing interest in a follow-up that was ultimately rejected.
Several directors were approached before Chung was hired in December 2022.
The cast joined in early-2023 and filming took place around Oklahoma that
summer, with a brief hiatus due to the SAG-AFTRA strike.
Twisters premiered at the Cineworld Leicester Square in London on July 8,
2024, and was released internationally by Warner Bros.
Pictures on July 10 and in the United States and
Canada by Universal Pictures on July 19.
It received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed $372.3 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of tornado, twister, disaster movie, cyclone.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.